thecontentauthority.com 2017-12-03

# Privacy Policy | The Content Authority

We are committed to protecting your personal information and we do not share this information unless otherwise required by law. This policy provides our statement of how and why we use personally identifiable information. We do not sell or trade any information we collect through the use of our website. 

### Information We Collect

You may provide certain personally identifiable information when you register on our site or place an order. When using our site, you may be asked to enter your name, mailing address, e-mail address, tax information, or PayPal® information. This information is necessary to provide you with the services offered through our site and it is protected under this privacy policy. We may collect information such as IP address, access times, and browser types. This information is solely used to enhance and maintain the quality of our site. 

### How We Use The Information We Collect

Personally identifiable information is used solely for business purposes such as billing, payment of services, and any tax-related purposes. We may use the information to keep you updated and informed about any changes in services or policy changes. In addition,we may send information on new products or services through email. Since we use PayPal® for billing purposes and payment purposes, we do provide Paypal®. with necessary information to ensure proper billing and payment. 

### How we protect Your information

We take reasonable and customary measures to provide for the protection of your personally identifiable information and other data. We use appropriate electronic, physical, and administrative procedures to safeguard against loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information. While we have the necessary safeguards to keep your data secure in place, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the Internet. When providing personally identifiable information and other data over the Internet, you do so at your own risk. 

### Disclosure of information to outside parties?

As previously mentioned, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to any outside parties. We may be required by law to do so in the event of a lawsuit or other legal action. We may choose to disclose personally identifiable information if we believe doing so will protect the right, property or safety of our site and its users. 

### Third-Party Service Providers

Our privacy policy does not apply to third-party service providers. Third-party providers shape their own privacy policies and may disclose the use of your personally identifiable information. We are not responsible for the use and dissemination of your information by any third-party service providers. 

### Children’s Privacy

We encourage persons under the age of 18 to obtain parental consent before utilizing the services of any web site including ours. We do not condone or allow the collection of Personally Identifiable Information of persons under 18 years of age. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

### Changes and Updates

We may update or change this policy at our discretion. We will post updates and changes to this page and we encourage you to review the policy regularly. Your continued use of our services indicates your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Information

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy by email at  **support@thecontentauthority.com** , or by sending postal mail to: **The Content Authority – P.O. Box 2031 Cranberry Township, PA 16066**
